信徒
*就算知道世界是黑暗的*
*Even know the world is dark*
*也要試著喜歡它*
*try to like a little part.*
■
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
*不要東躲西藏*
*Don't go, run and hide.*
翻譯：阿飄    木淺薰薰薰    持久久久君    Silence    筱妤
*獻出我的心*
*Give a little of my heart*
*它就能有節奏地*
*only then the beat will start*
翻譯：青椒    北灣    燕窩窩窩頭   MythCreator   衛衛衛老哥
*永跳不止*
*keepin' me in time*
翻譯：七個柚子醬    香茗小焙    瀟湘月影    DDDustD
*生命如此短暫*
*Life doesn't wait for long.*
校對：sienna   某羽   飄雪的天空   somehacker  王小麥
時間軸：阿丹  雪貴人  后期：魚骨頭  總監：sienna  某羽
菠  你唱的什么歌
Hey Bo. W-what song is that?
我夢里的歌
It's from my dream.
-很好聽哦  -*為什么...*
- That's sweet. - *Why...*
特蕾西發了郵件
Oh, Tracy emailed me.
新沙發來了
The new couch came in.
比我想象中更綠一點
That's like... a little greener than I thought.
可能是照片的緣故吧
Probably just the pictures.
走開
Go around.
這家伙
Ah, this guy.
天吶
Oh, my god!
怎么了
What's going on?
菠  你還好嗎  菠
Bo, are you OK, Bo?
他還在跟著我們
He's still on us.
趴下  抓牢車子
Keep down, keep on this.
抓緊了 抓緊
Hang on! Hang on!
美琪
Maggie,
你還好嗎
are you OK?
帶菠走
Take Bo.
帶她走
Take her.
打電話給錢寧
Call Channing
告訴他他們找到她了
They found her.
-我來了  -她失去意識了
- I'm coming. - She's unconscious.
別擔心  我來了
Don't worry. I'm coming.
天哪
Oh my God.
你還好嗎
Are you OK?
傷到哪里了嗎
Are you hurt?
我需要急救
I need an ambulance.
也許這能讓你舒服一點
Maybe this will help.
別傷害她
Don't hurt her.
她還是個孩子
She's just a little girl.
求你了
Please...
我不在乎
I don't care.
把她放下
Put her down.
Put her down!
別移動她
Don't move her.
我是醫生
I'm a doctor.
快打急救電話
Somebody call 911.
救護車來了
An ambulance is coming.
謝天謝地
Oh, thank God!
你可以告訴救護員  你還好嗎
You can tell service. Are you OK?
金斯蘭監獄  佐治亞州
請
Please.
謝謝
Thank you.
醒醒  塔特  伙計  你的神父來了
Weak up, Tate, man. Your priest is here.
我們總這么玩
It's a little game we'd like to play.
你在里面沒問題吧
You gotta be ok in here?
沒問題  謝謝
Fine... thank you.
晚上好
Good evening.
我沒要求見神父
I didn't ask for a priest.
你有相當長的暴力史  塔特先生
You have such a long history of violence, Mr. Tate.
第一次被捕是十四歲
First arrested in 14,
之后還因為搶劫和傷人多次入獄
after that, numerous arrests, robbery and assault.
現在  你因兩起謀殺罪
And now you are being excuted for two counts
將在半小時內被處決
of felony murders in 30 minutes,
而你沒什么要懺悔的嗎
and you have nothing to confess?
我是無辜的  我是被陷害的
I'm innocent. I was set up.
不過貌似沒人相信吧
No one seems to believe you, do they?
從來沒人相信過你
No one ever did.
今天行刑  卻沒有家人朋友來看你
No friends or family come to be with you today,
你服刑這七年  也從未有人來過
nor in seven years that you have been here.
維持活下去的希望都是很難的吧
Must be very difficult to maintain hope.
包括想要記住曾經的你
Remember who you once were.
我不需要懺悔
I don't need a confession.
那就最好不過了
Well, thank God to that.
你生存的世界里
You live in the world
每個人都在尋求寬恕
where everyone wants forgiveness,
但是無人尋得
but no one has permission.
你想怎么樣
What do you want?
我是來幫你逃獄的
I'm here to help you escape.
主要是割傷和挫傷對吧
Mostly cuts and bruises, right?
沒錯  但她還沒恢復意識
Yeah, but she's still unconscious.
我們要確保沒有內傷
We need to make sure there is no internal injuries.
停下
Stop.
請停下
Please stop.
她醒了
She woke up.
那是她的大腦圖嗎  出錯了吧
That's her... brain? That can't be right.
-大腦系統確實在運作  -再測一次
- System is functioning. - Check it again.
停下
Stop it.
忍耐一下  馬上就好
Just one minute, please.
機器沒問題
No, we are good here.
很奇怪  對嗎
It's weird, right?
停下
Stop it!
快關掉
Turn it off!
謝謝
Thank you.
我要是答應了  你有什么要求呢
So if I say yes, what's the catch.
我來不僅是為了還你自由
Well, I'm not just freeing you,
還要給你份工作
I'm hiring you.
昨晚一男一女死于車禍
Last night a man and woman died in a car accident,
他們是一個叫菠的小女孩的養父母
they were foster parents to a little girl name Bo.
這行不通的
Guys, this is not gonna work.
溫特  小心信號聲
Winter, careful with the beeps.
但那不是場意外
But this wasn't an accident,
有人想要綁架這個小女孩卻失敗了
it was a failed attempt to kidnap this little girl.
她現在在圣安妮醫院  我們得在別人之前
Now she is in St.Anne's hospital and we need to get there
趕過去
before the others do.
跟你說吧
Yeah, well, guess what,
我不是個綁匪
I'm not a kidnaper.
我沒有要你綁架她
I'm not asking you to kidnap her.
我來請你救她
I'm asking you to save her.
這個小女孩非常重要
This little girl is very important,
而你還有4分54秒的時間逃出去
and you'll have four minutes and 54 seconds to escape.
你他媽在說什么
What the hell are you talking about?
你覺得這很好玩嗎
Huh, you think this is funny?
你有考慮嗎  還是只是固執己見
Are you think or just stubborn.
我可在給你一條出路
I'm offering you a way out.
離牧師遠一點
Hey, away from the priest!
4分28秒
Four minutes twenty-eight seconds.
我憑什么相信你
Why would I trust you, huh?
不能相信那些所謂的朋友
You don't happen to believe in people, you so called friends.
-夠了  -你以為我為什么在這
-Enough - Why do you think I'm here, huh?
-好了嗎  -好了
- All clear? - Clear.
沒有心跳
No rhythm.
給我一支腎上腺素  一支阿托品[含顛茄]
All right, give me one of EPI, one of atropine.
-好了嗎  -好了
- All clear? - Clear.
醫生  可以結束了吧
Doctor, are you calling in?
不
No.
醫生
Doctor.
死亡時間  晚上11點58分
11:58 p.m.
你已經盡力了
You did everything you could.
很遺憾  醫生
I'm sorry, doctor.
我雖行過死蔭的幽谷
Yeah, though I walk through the valley of shadow and death,
出自舊約圣經《詩篇》第二十三章
通常是為死刑犯最后的禱詞
也不怕遭害
I shall fear no evil.
你還有五十秒
You have 50 seconds.
什么意思  他們說只是打砸搶
What does it mean, they said is was just a smash and grab.
他們陷害了我
They frammed me.
不關我的事
I don't care.
四十秒
40 seconds.
二十秒
20 seconds.
為什么是我
Why me?
因為我信任你
Because I believe in you.
好
Okay.
哈利路亞
Hallelujah.
關燈  關閉系統
Lights out, and systems down.
手呢  把你手給我
All right, hands. Gimme hands.
還有腳鐐
Feet, feet.
很好  現在打他
Good, good. Now, hit him.
-來  打我  -賤人
- Come on, hit me. - Son of a bitch.
接著
Take it. Now,
往左邊走  左邊
Down to the left, go left, to the left.
快點  我們得快點
Come one. Let's hurry
麥斯奇
Masky.
聽5
他  他往那邊跑了
He... he went that way.
他往那邊跑了
He went that way. He went that way.
愿平靜與你同在
Peace be with you.
開始行動
Let's go.
住手  住手
All right. Stop. Stop.
我也"很高興"見到你
Yeah, nice to meet you too.
好了  住手  關了它
All right, all right. Knock it off. Knock it off.
早上好  我叫溫特
Good morning. I'm Winter.
我們要飛幾個小時  飛機上聊吧
We'll fly for a couple hours and we'll talk.
這計劃如何
How's that for a plan?
我沒讓你們銬著他
I didn't ask for cuffs.
她有點過于"積極"了
Yeah, she's a bit exuberant.
你根本不了解我
You don't know me at all.
解開他的手銬
Uncuff him.
為什么選他  他是個殺人犯
Why him? He's a murderer.
為什么不選我
Why not me.
這個我們晚點再說
Let's talk about this later.
你叫菠對嗎
You're Bo, right?
我是庫里安醫生  是這里的住院醫師
I'm Doctor Kurian, a resident here.
這烏龜很可愛
That's a cute turtle.
他叫斯坦利
His name's Stanley.
是我媽媽送給我的
My mom gave him to me.
我的親生媽媽
My real mom.
可我不記得她了
I don't remember her.
你還需要做幾項檢查  但是
So you're gonna need a few more tests, but...
你不會有事的
you're gonna be OK.
還有其他的事情
But there're some other things...
跟我說就好
I can in charge.
那場車禍很嚴重
That was a very bad crash.
他們死了
They're dead.
對此我很遺憾
I'm so sorry.
他們才做了我兩個星期的父母
They were my parents for only two weeks.
他們那么和藹
They were so nice.
另一個房間的病人
The man in the another room.
那不是你的錯
It's not your fault.
你說什么
Excuse me?
你不能辭職
You can't quit.
你是個好醫生
You're a good doctor.
你救了絲尼格
You saved Senga.
誰是絲尼格
Who's Senga?
拜托  你還照顧過他
Come on. You took care of him.
你累了  菠
You're tired, Bo.
我晚點再來看你
I'll check on you later. OK?
Senga怎么樣了
How is Senga doing?
抱歉  我不認識叫絲尼格的人
I'm sorry, I don't know anyone named Senga.
好好休息一會吧
Get some rest.
我是斯古洛斯
Skouras.
斯古洛斯  你好
Hello, Skouras.
那個小女孩現在圣安妮醫院里
The girl's at St. Anne's hospital.
知道了  我明天就回去
I know. I'll be back tomorrow.
明天就太遲了
Tomorrow will be too late.
溫特會保護她的
Winter will be back for her.
-彌爾頓·溫特嗎  -是
- Milton Winter? - Hmmm.
他已經死了
He’s dead.
他就想讓大家這么認為
That’s what he wants everyone to think.
我說得很明白
I was very clear.
我今晚不工作  今天是我媽媽生日
Tonight I have to be out of pocket. It's my mother's birthday.
據說是在圣安妮醫院的八樓
It said St. Anne's hospital on the eighth floor.
抓到她后聯系我  謝謝
Call me when you have her. Thank you.
我很榮幸將今年的人道主義獎頒給
羅曼·斯古洛斯
自打菠出生  就一直有神秘現象發生
Unexplainable phenomena have been part of Bo's life since she was born.
這些現象無法預測
These events are unpredictable
似乎是和她的情緒有關
and seem to be connected to her emotions.
現在她還控制不了那力量
Now, she has no control of it.
她會長大成才的
But she is going to become the person she is going to be.
有個被冤入獄的人
There's a guy was wronged in prison.
他能掰彎勺子
He can bend spoons.
塔特先生  這是很非常真實的
This is very real, Mr.Tate.
被冤入獄的那位也是真的
The wronged is real too.
他還可以掰彎小刀
He could bend knives though.
我們想在適當的時候
We want to share her with the world
讓她為世界所用
at just the right moment.
有權勢的人會試圖綁架她
People would try to kidnap her. Very powerful people.
他們想把她全部天賦都據為己用
They want all of her talents for themselves.
他們覺得控制了她的能力
They think that whoever controls her abilities
就控制了世界
will control the world.
就算這都是真的
Even if all of it is true,
為什么選我
why me?
最新科技  全球定位追蹤裝置
State of the art, GPS tracking device.
我們能確切地知道你在哪
We'll know where you are, plus you minus two feet.
那只是為了保證你做完任務會回來
That's just to make sure you maintain your end in the barn.
如果想脫下它  只能砍掉自己的腿
And if you want it off, you have to chop off your leg.
或許我會咬掉它
Or maybe I'll chew it off.
請自便
Be my guest.
五分鐘后降落
Clear to land in five minutes.
你會給我配槍吧
You're gonna give me a gun, right?
塔特先生  你和好人共事
You don't do guns, Mr. Tate,
用不上槍
with the good guys.
是真的嗎  你辭職了
Is it true? You gave notice?
不只是因為這件事吧
It's not just about this, is it?
我為你感到遺憾
Sorry to hear that.
祝爺爺早日康復
她應該在重癥監護病房
We think she's in ICU.
穿過急診室
Going through the ER,
帶她回來  然后跟桑托斯會合
bring her back, and meet Santos there.
讓他躺下吧  開始行動
Put him down, let's go.
行動  現在正好有機會
Go now. We got a window.
什么狀況
What do we got?
從梯子上跌落  受力兩臂有挫傷
Fall off a ladder. Contusion on his based arms.
不過還算穩定
But he's stable.
還算好  還有情況更糟的  走吧
Good part, given that we have blood processing. Let's move.
走吧  快點
Let's move, come on. Let's go.
-抱歉  -不好意思
- Sorry. - Excuse me.
打擾一下  里面那個女孩去哪里了
Excuse me. Where's the girl that was in there?
狀況穩定了  轉移到了普通病房
She's stable. They moved her.
你好臭
You stink.
我摔進了下水道
Fell on a sewer.
不過他們給我洗過了
But they washed me off.
還是好臭
You still stink.
我不臭
I don't.
很臭
You do.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
塔特
Tate.
你剛才在哭
You were crying.
沒哭
No, I wasn't.
肯定哭了
Yes, you were.
我撞到頭
Well, I hit my head.
你臉上的傷是假的
Those bruises are fake.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
因為  你根本不覺得疼
Because, you're not feeling any pain.
我能摸一下嗎
Can I touch them?
不行
No. Ow.
你看  我很疼的
You see? It hurts a lot.
該走了
We have to go.
你是我的新養父嗎
Are you my new foster dad?
不是
No.
很好  你太臭了
Good, because you stink.
這已經說過了
Yeah. We established that.
我不會跟你走的
I'm not going with you.
你就得跟我走  溫特說了你必須跟我走
Yes, you are. Winter says you have to come with me.
彌爾頓嗎
Milton?
是溫特
Winter.
他叫彌爾頓·溫特
Milton Winter.
他在哪里
Where is he?
我帶你去找他
I'm taking you to him.
好
Okay.
你知道你為什么哭嗎
You know why you were crying?
跟你說過了  傷很疼
I told you, it hurts.
不  那是因為你想起來了你是個好人
No. You remembered that you are the good ones.
好了  我們快走
Come on. Let's go.
急什么
God.
你們要去哪兒
Where are you going?
帶她去拍個片子
Eh...take her to radiology.
那好  我跟你們一起去
Of course. I'll walk with you.
你感覺怎么樣
How are you feeling?
挺好的
Good.
別擔心  我會帶你過去的
Don't worry. I'll take you.
還是我來吧
I have to do it.
醫院規定
Hospital policy.
還是我帶她去吧
You know what? I'm gonna take her to go.
你會害我丟了工作的
I can lose my job.
艾蘭醫生
Dr...Eillen.
你還好吧
You alright?
你臉色有些發白
You look a little pale.
我可不想良心不安
Please, I don't want to have the itchy backs.
我就如你所愿
No problem.
小孩子別這么調皮
Aw! Not cool.
快跑  快跑
Come on! Come on!
從那邊走
Go, go, go, go, go.
快趴下  別開槍
Get down. Don't shot.
這邊  快點
This way! Hurry!
停車
Hey, stop!
麻煩停車
Stop, please.
她會平安無事嗎
Do you think she's gonna be OK?
-誰  -追我們的那個女人
- Who? - That lady.
我在她屁股上狠狠扎了一針
I stabbed her hard in the butt.
她會沒事的  我才不在乎
She would be fine. Who cares?
-我們這是去哪  -我不知道
- Where are we going? - I don't know.
-彌爾頓在哪  -我說了不知道
- Where's Milton? - I don't know.
能不能安靜一會
Please stop talking for a second.
城市理發店
我知道絲尼格是誰
I know who Senga is.
你說什么
What?
絲尼格
Senga.
她不是普通病人
She's not a normal patient.
我們得告訴特里醫生  這樣他就不會辭職了
We have to find Dr.Terry and tell him, so he won't quit.
你女兒下車了
Your daughter. She's gone.
她不是我女兒
She's not my daughter.
這下好了
Swell.
你回來晚了
You're late.
-我自己也有安排  -很抱歉
- I have a life too, you know? - I'm sorry.
他吃飯了嗎
Did he eat?
我盡力了  可他沒吃多少
Not much. I've tried, though.
你可以周日再付我錢
You can pay me on Sunday.
謝謝你  卡門
Thank you, Carmen.
嘿  爸爸
Hey, dad.
有個今天病人死了
A man died today.
我想救他  但沒成功
Tried to save him but I couldn't.
這是第一次
First time, you know.
我也不知道  以前也看過人死  但
I don't know. I've seen people die before, but--
這個人  我真的很想救他
This guy, I wish that I could save.
我想你說得對
I guess you're right.
還記得你以前總跟我說的話嗎
Remember what you used to say to me?
不記得了嗎
No?
我記得
I do.
你說就算我是地球上最后一個醫生
Say you wouldn't come to me,
你也不會來找我看病
if I was the last doctor on earth.
你是對的
You were right.
你永遠是對的
You're always right, man.
你總是那么強壯
You're always so strong,
有那么多想法
so full of opinions.
所以你生病后
So when you got sick,
我總想著要治好你
I was gonna fix you.
我總是  總是想讓你恢復健康
I was gonna-- I was gonna cure you.
我要讓你知道你錯了
You know, I was gonna show you, you were wrong.
而你會感謝我
And you're gonna thank me.
如果知道我今天辭職了  你會很開心吧
You'd be happy to know that I quit today.
你總是要爭到最后做贏的那一個
See, you always have the last word.
現在你卻沒法再說了
You know what, you can't say it.
你在干什么呢
What're you doing?
我要找地址
I needed an address.
你不能像那樣直接跑掉
You can't just run away like that.
我們要去奧斯維奧街14-22號
We need to go to 14-22, Auswell Street.
你在胡言亂語些什么
What are you talking about?
我得告訴特里醫生關于絲尼格的事
I need to talk to Dr.Terry about Segna.
你這個小屁孩能閉嘴聽我講話嗎
Can you shut up and listen to me for a sec, you little brat!
沒有人在乎
Nobody cares!
你那21任養父母也不在乎
Nor do your 21st forster parents.
你真刻薄
You are mean.
而且你很傻  英語說得也不好
And you're being stupid, and you have English problems.
你們倆  快進來  我們走
Hey, you guys, get in, let's go!
-錢寧  -我們得趕快走  快
- Channing! - Come on, we gotta go, we gotta go.
開車
Let's go.
你們去哪兒了
Where the hell were you?
我們應該回救護車上的
We were supposed to be back at the ambulance.
但我們回不去
Yeah, we couldn't be there,
有個家伙把我打了個半死
'cause some guy was beating the crap out of me.
不是家伙  是個女的
It wasn't a guy, it was a girl.
-我就是說  -一個女的把你打了個半死
- Yeah, I just meant-- - A girl beat the crap out of you.
好吧  是的
Okay, yeah.
但那個女的  長得很高大
But it was-- a big girl.
她一點都不高大
She wasn't big.
在這兒
In here.
我來吧
Give me that.
彌爾頓
Milton！
過來讓我抱抱
Come and see me.
你又重了
How could you? You're getting bigger.
才沒有  我兩周之前才和你見過
No, I'm not! I saw you two weeks ago.
錢寧  帶菠去看看新衣服  好嗎
Listen Channing, go and show Bo new clothes, would you?
我有些很漂亮的
I've got some great stuff.
做得好
Well done.
-塔特先生  -我的腳環
- Mr. Tate. - My bracelet,
-把它拿掉  -沒那么簡單
- I want it off. - It's not that simple.
我們有過協定
We had a deal.
我說的是你為我工作
I said you come work for me.
你的工作我已經做完了
Yeah, and I did your work.
你的工作才剛開始
Your work has just begun.
我相信你已經注意到了
I'm sure you noticed that
菠是個非常特殊的女孩
Bo is a very special little girl.
你的工作是保護她
Your job is to protect her,
確保她的安全
keep her safe.
不要讓那個女人傷害她嗎
What, from that woman?
那個女人  以及她所效力的那些人
That woman, and all the people that woman works for.
他會成為我的新養父嗎
Is he gonna be my new foster dad?
稍等  寶貝
In a second, sweetheart.
他很兇  而且身上很臭
He is mean, and he stinks.
我掉到下水道里了  我都告訴你了
I fell on a sewer, I told you.
你看  她也不想和我待在一起
You see, she doesn't wanna be with me either.
我們會幫忙的
We'll be helping, you know.
不過最重要的責任  例如她的健康
But the ultimate responsibility for her well being, her health,
以及她的教育  那是你的任務
her education, that belongs to you.
溫特  我想和你待在一起
Winter, I want to stay with you,
過來寶貝  過來
Come here sweetheart, come here.
聽著
Now listen,
我們已經談過了  還記得嗎
we talked about this, remember?
如果我接受的話  這工作需要幾個星期
So if I say yes, how many weeks is this job supposed to last?
幾個星期
Weeks?
難道要幾個月嗎
So what, months?
這會是你一生中最精彩的幾年
It'll be the best years of your life.
我們用了五年時間才找到線索
It took us five years to find the Adam's rolling
而你只用了一天就跟丟了嗎
and you lost her in one day?
你夠了  蠢貨  發現什么了嗎
Come on twat, what do you have?
巴爾的摩地區僅有的相關資料是
The only relevant data in Baltimore is
溫特在死前一年購買的房產
a property that Winter bought one year before he died.
地址是新柯克街
The address is 16-105,
16-105號  看上去像個倉庫
New Kirk Street. It looks like a warehouse,
我現在把坐標發到你的GPS上
I'm sending the coordinates to your GPS now.
很好  轉一圈
Yeah, take a spin.
你看起來真漂亮
You look great.
-謝謝  -你喜歡嗎
- Thank you. - Do you like it?
對方的本事大得很
The other side is very resourceful.
盡量避免使用電話和其他電子設備
Keep you use cell phone and other electronics to a minimum.
錢寧會監控你的行蹤和進展
Channing will monitor your whereabouts, your progress.
你知道我還沒同意吧
You realise I haven't agreed any of this yet.
你當然同意了
Oh yes, you have.
滿世界都在通緝你
You are all over the airwaves.
聯調局  警察  所有人都在找你
FBI, police, everybody is looking for you.
也許我可以碰碰運氣
Maybe I'll take my chances.
你出去之后十分鐘都堅持不了
You won't last ten minutes out there.
他們一看到你就會射殺你
They'll shoot you on sight.
但是有了我們的幫助  你就不用擔心了
But, that won't happen now with our help.
我們不是超級英雄
We are not superheros.
但我們是勤奮努力的人
But we are dedicated and hardworking people.
我們可以保護你
We can protect you.
你還沒有回答我的問題
You still haven't answered my question.
為什么選我
Why me?
這是給你的
That is for you.
我要你好好照顧她
I want you to take good care of her,
教育她  給她吃有機食品
educate her, good oganic food,
讓她住舒服的地方
comfy accommodations.
你從現在開始要撫養她
You are gonna be raising her now.
我需要一把槍
I need a gun.
你已經說過了
You talked about that already.
塔特先生
Mr. Tate.
你第一次看到她時就有所感覺  對嗎
When you first saw her, you felt something, didn't you?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你感覺到了什么
What did you feel?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不喜歡小孩
I don't like kids.
怎么了
What's up?
帶上菠
Get Bo.
他們怎么找到我們的
How did they find us?
請問要去哪一層
Which floor, please?
快
Quickly!
-斯坦利  -別管了
- Stanley! - No, leave him.
-別撿了  快走  -不  斯坦利
- Stop, come on. - No, no. Stanley!
-快點  -快走
- Hurry up, hurry up. - Go, go, go.
-不  -塔特
- No. - Tate
塔特
Tate.
快過來
Come on, please.
斯坦利
Stanley!
科里  他們之前在這里  現在走了
They were here and now they're gone, Corey.
他們還能去什么地方
Where else will they go?
查查別的房子  別的人
Check any other properties, people,
任何別的地方
any other locations.
再查查
Check it again.
我等著
I'll wait.
不過快一點
Just be quick about it.
你好啊  拇指姑娘
Hello, Thumbelina
放開她
Let her go!
溫特
Winter！
我以為你不打女人
I thought you didn't hit girls.
現在打了
Well, I do now
塔特
Tate!
過來
Come on!
塔特
Tate!
幫幫他
Help him!
不
No!
快走  快走
Go, go, go!
快走
Go!
-錢怎么辦  -別管錢了
- What about the cash? - Forget the cash.
快走
Come on!
快走  快走
Go, go, go, go, go!
怎么回事  我不明白
What happened? I don't understand.
沒事了  沒事了  寶貝
It's ok, it's ok, sweetheart.
就是鬧鬼而已
It's just like all the other spook,
只是有點嚇人  不過沒事了
it's just a-- a little bit-- but that's all.
-溫特  -再快點  快走
- Winter. - Faster! Go, go, go!
塔特先生
Mr. Tate.
我們所有的據點都不安全了
All our locations, they were compromised.
你們得不斷轉移
You have to keep moving from place to place.
我們會拖住她
We will defer her.
你們現在就得下車
You gotta get out right now.
我們要去哪兒
Where do we go?
菠知道
Bo knows!
快下車
Get out!
別相信任何人  我們會去找你們
Don't trust anyone. We'll try to find you.
彌爾頓
Milton!
快走  帶上錢
Fast, go, go! Take this money.
帶上錢  躲那兒去  快走
Take this money. Down there. Go! Go!
14-20
14-20.
120美元要過三年
120 bucks for the next 3 years.
真不錯
It's well.
還沒到嗎
Are we there yet?
到了
Yeah, we're here.
剛才那事兒  你怎么做到的
That thing back there, how'd you do that?
你指什么
What do you mean?
就是剛才那群鳥  很詭異  到底是怎么回事
That spooky thing, the thing with the birds, what was that?
那經常發生嗎
Does that happen a lot?
我不想提那事
I don't want to talk about it.
這里還有嗎
We got some more down here?
你說餅干嗎
You mean for cookies?
什么
What?
-特里  -不行  咱們走
- Terry. - No, come on.
菠  你在這干什么
Bo, what are you doing here?
我需要跟你說絲尼格的事
I need talk to you about Senga.
我朋友需要幫助
My friend needs help.
發生了什么事
What heppened?
一個壞女人開槍打了他
A mean woman shot him.
-你受了槍傷  -不算什么  我沒事
- You were shot? - It's nothing, I'm fine.
他是個醫生
He's a doctor,
一個非常出色的醫生
a really good doctor.
如果你中了槍  我們必須報警
If you were shot, we'll have to report it to the police.
能先幫我止一下血嗎
Well, can you stop the bleeding first?
非常感謝
I'd appreciate that.
好吧  進屋吧
All right, come inside.
我這沒有麻醉劑
I don't have any anesthetic.
縫上就行
Just sew it up.
好吧  坐到桌子上
All right, have a seat on the table,
掀起你的襯衫
lift up your shirt.
小心
Look out.
他是你父親
He's your father.
不省人事了
Barely conscious,
時日不多了
almost gone.
他很為你自豪
He's proud of you.
不  他不會
No, he isn't.
你不能辭職
You can't quit.
絲尼格怎么辦
What about Senga?
我告訴過你我不知道那是誰
I told you I don't know who that is.
-我知道  -抗生素
- I know. - Antibiotic.
我以為你認識絲尼格
I thought you knew Senga.
我有時會弄錯
Sometimes I get things wrong.
再深呼吸一次
Take a deep breath again.
你現在還不認識她
You don't know her yet,
但你會認識的
but you will.
這可能會有點疼
It's gonna hurt a little bit.
請盡量不要動
Try not to move, please.
有一天她會病得很厲害
One day she'll be really sick,
但你能救她
but you'll save her.
因為你她才能活下去
She'll live because of you.
她是個歌手
She's a singer.
絲尼格是個歌手
Senga is a singer.
對  她非常棒
Yeah, she's really good.
人們難過的時候
When people are having a hard time,
她的音樂能讓他們開心起來
her music will make them feel happy.
你會治好她
You'll fix her.
好樣的
You're doing great.
你會治好很多人
You'll fix a lot of people.
就像你救治他這樣
Same way you're fixing him.
再縫一針就沒事了
One more you will be all right.
你父親認為你是個好醫生
Your father thinks you're a good doctor.
他知道你努力想治好他
He knows you tried to save him.
他知道他之前錯了
He knows he was wrong.
他很抱歉從沒說過
And he's sorry he never said it.
他愛你
He loves you.
他相信你
He believes in you.
只是擦傷
The bullet barely nicked you.
別沾水  盡量別搬東西
Keep it dry, try not to carry anything.
-要報警嗎  -算了
- Police? - It's fine.
她怎么知道這些事
How does she know all of this?
我也不知道  伙計
I don't know, man,
她就是這么討人厭
she is a pain in the ass.
特里
Terry.
好的  先進行胸外按壓  準備好手術室
OK, get the NCCR, just prepare the OR,
我十分鐘內趕到
I'll be there in ten minutes.
醫院人手不足
They are short-staffed.
他們需要我
They need me.
穿上運動衫  快點
Get that sweat shirt, come on.
卡門  我是亞當
Hey Carmen, it's Adam.
我知道事出突然  但你得過來一趟
I know it's short noticed but I need you to come over.
我被叫去醫院了
I got called into the hospital.
謝謝  非常感謝
Thank you, thank you so much.
-再見了  菠  -再見
- Goodbye, Bo. - Bye.
謝了
Thanks.
好吧  我們到底去哪
OK, now where do we really go?
費城
Philadelphia.
我脾氣不好
Look, I was very touchy,
但如果你想跟我走  去另一個城市
but if this is gonna work, we're gonna get to a new town,
就得定幾條規矩  好嗎
we're gonna need some rules, okay?
好吧
Okay.
第一
Number one,
那個醫生不關你的事
that doctor guy wasn't your business,
你多管閑事了
you're nosy.
-是他把你治好的  -我知道
- He fixed you. - Yeah,
他是個好人
and that's fine and all.
但到了別的地方  你少管別人的事
But when we get somewhere, you need to mind your own business.
聽明白了嗎
You understand me?
有姑娘掉進河里怎么辦
What if a girl falls into a river?
我不在乎  快向我保證
I don't care. Now, promise.
如果我看到有人在路上逆行
What if I saw a man walking on wrong side of the road,
然后那天特別熱
and it's realy hot...
熱到掉個硬幣
if he drop a penny...
都能直接融化在路上
they get stuck on the melting road.
他去撿硬幣手被黏住
What if his hand get stuck,
而一輛卡車正迎面而來
and a truck is coming.
-這根本不可能  -如果真的發生了呢
- That's never happening. - But what if it did...
來電  媽媽
-她叫什么名字  -艾格尼絲
- What is her name? - Agnes.
艾格尼絲
Agnes.
溫特  手背怎么樣了
Winter. How is the back hand.
她又被保護起來了
She is protected again.
你沒機會了
You lost your chance.
被塔特保護著
Protected by Tate.
我得說這有點出人意料啊
I have to admit that was a surprise.
你知道這事早晚會出岔子的
You know it's gonna blow up in your face.
斯古洛斯越逼越近了
Skouras is closing in.
我真不敢相信咱們以前居然和那種人一伙
I can't believe we used to be partner with that guy.
過往總是
Well... the past was a very
很神奇的  親愛的
tricky place, my dear.
我們得不斷地讓他們在各城市間轉移
We have to move them from town to town.
不行  那太冒險了
No. It's incredible risky.
但是我們向好處看
But let's look on the bright side,
想想那些她一路上能夠幫助到的人吧
think of all the people she will help along the way.
可你找了個死刑犯當她同伴
But you put her with a death row inmate.
不  那個人
No... I put her...
是她父親
with her father.
如果有月亮的碎片砸到了一間房子里
What if the piece of moon crashes in to a house,
那里他們把蜘蛛關在籠子里  籠子壞了
and they keep the spider in the cage, but the cage breaks...
然后尼桑姆那里有個種田人
and the people of the Neatham have grower
對蜘蛛過敏呢
who's allergic to spiders.
你這句話槽點太多了
I don't know where to start with that one.
第二規矩是什么
What's rule number two.
-一切照我說的做  -好的
- Always do what I said. - OK.
但是  如果我們正呆在冰屋里
But... what if we are in a Igloo,
而你患上了寒冷腫瘤什么的
and you have a cold carcinoma... I think,
然后你叫我點蠟燭  可我聞到了瓦斯味
and you tell me to light the candle, but I smelled gas.
這樣啊  一定要點蠟燭
You know what, light the candle.
艾格尼絲
絲尼格
一切都會好起來的
It's gonna be ok.